Vonnegut, Bernard; Papers ua902.068
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Project Cirrus, 1891-1985; Undated; 1; 4.25 cubic ft.
  - Reprints, Sublimation of Outdoor Air and Seeded Sublimation, Undated (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 27)
  - Reprints, SUNY Weatherwise - Simple Experiments in Atmospheric Physics, 1955 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 28)
  - Reprints, Surface Tension of Small Droplets of Water from Volmer and Flood's Nucleation Data, 1949 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 29)
  - Reprints, Symposium on Artificial Rain, 1951 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 30)
  - Reprints, The Crystalline Structure of Ice, Undated (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 31)
  - Reprints, The Preparation of Colloidal AgI Water-Suspension for Nucleation of Supercooled Clouds, 1949 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 32)
  - Reprints, The Problem of Artificial Rain on the Globe, 1948 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 33)
  - Reprints, Trilliat Articles, 1948-1949 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 34)
  - Reprints, Untitled French Report, 1949 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 35)
  - Reprints, Weather, 1949 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 36)
  - Reprints, Weatherwise, 1949 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 37)
  - Research, Aerosol Detection Methods, 1950 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 38)
  - Research, Air Plane Icing, 1946 (Box 4 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 39)
  - Research, Atmosphere (General), 1945; 1947-1948; 1952 (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 1)
  - Research, Atmospheric Electrification, 1954; 1956 (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 2)
  - Research, Atmospheric Particle Research, 1952 (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 3)
  - Research, Electrical Atomization, 1951 (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 4)
  - Research, Heated Filament Aerosol Report, Undated (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
  - Research, Hot Wire Report and Data, Undated (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
  - Research, Nucleation Data Folder/Report, 1947 (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 7)
  - Seeding Flights, Cloud Seeding Technique Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 5 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 8)
  - Seeding Flights, Air Speed/ Temperature/Nuclei Counter Research, 1949-1950 (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 1)
  - Seeding Flights, Faust, 1949 (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 2)
  - Seeding Flights, Flight #105 Photo Report, 1949 (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 3)
  - Seeding Flights, Flight #57 Paper, Undated (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 4)
  - Seeding Flights, Flight #57 Report, 1948 (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
  - Technical Diagrams, 1948 (Flat-file 1)
  - Technical Diagrams, 1948; Undated (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
  - Untitled, Filament, Undated (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 7)
  - Untitled, Transparencies, Undated (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 8)
  - Voltmeter Instruction Manual, Undated (Box 6 (1-Project Cirrus), Folder 9)
- NASA Experiments, 1976-1991; Undated; 2; 1.68 cubic ft.
  Series 2 documents the NOSL (Nighttime/Daylight Optical Survey of Thunderstorm Lightning) experiment, a large-scale project undertaken by NASA during the early 1980s, in which astronauts recorded and documented thunderstorm and lightning activity from the Earth's orbit. Dr. Vonnegut, who proposed the project, utilized the photographs and data in his continuing research on thunderstorms and electrification theory.
  The series contains data, reports, correspondence, press releases, photographs, and NASA technical memoranda and shuttle specifications regarding the NOSL project. Crew activity plans and specifications are filed by flight number. Associated documents were kept with their respective flight number as much as possible. Additionally, memorabilia from one shuttle flight is incorporated, including a signed photograph from the astronauts who took part in the experiment.
  - Curtner, M.L. (Doc), 1978 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 1)
  - Equipment Information, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 2)
  - Equipment Information, 1977-1978 (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
  - Experiment Requirements Document, 1977 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 3)
  - Fiess, Mary, SUNY News Bureau, 1981-1989 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 4)
  - Flight Requirement Proposal - NASA, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 5)
  - Investigators Working Group Meeting, Johnson Space Center, October 25-26, 1978 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 6)
  - Investigators Working Group Meeting, Johnson Space Center, June 2-3, 1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 7)
  - Koutchmy, Serge - Salyut Lightning, 1983 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 8)
  - Lightning from Later Flights, 1985; 1991 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 9)
  - NASA Flights, 1980 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 10)
  - NASA Flight Summary Report - Flight #79-120, August 8, 1979 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 11)
  - NASA Memorabilia, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 12)
  - NASA Memorabilia, 1982 (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
  - NASA Publications, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 13)
  - NASA Technical Memorandum - Shuttle Observations, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 14)
  - New Yorker, "Lightning Strikes Seen from Satellite", 1976 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 15)
  - NOSL: Analysis of Data, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 16)
  - NOSL: Critical Design Review Meeting, August 17, 1978 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 17)
  - NOSL: Description, Gayle Weber and William Green, 1978 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 18)
  - NOSL: Description - Mary Fae McKay, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 19)
  - NOSL: Experiment, 1977 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 20)
  - NOSL: Experiment Implementation Plan (EIP), Undated (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 21)
  - NOSL: Follow-up Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 22)
  - NOSL: NASA Technical Memorandum 78261, 1980 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 23)
  - NOSL: Press Releases, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 24)
  - NOSL: Project Documents and Information, 1976-1990 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 25-28)
  - NOSL: Project Documents and Information, 1980; 1982; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
  - Operations Working Group Meeting, Johnson Space Center, November 8, 1977 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 29)
  - Operations Requirements Meetings, 1978 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 30)
  - OSTA-1: Experiments, 1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 31)
  - OSTA-1: Science and Data Management Review Meeting, February 25-26, 1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 32)
  - Personnel Access and Patch Requests, 1982 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 33)
  - Photographs, Flights 5 and 6, 1984 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 34)
  - Photographs, Thunderstorms in Brazil, 1984 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 35)
  - Press Stories, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 36)
  - Shuttle Altitude Charts, Undated (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 37)
  - Slides, 1982 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 38)
  - STS-2: ACSM-ASP Convention Presentation, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 39)
  - STS-2: Crew Activity Plan, Revision A, 1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 40)
  - STS-2: Crew Activity Plan, Revision B, 1981 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 41)
  - STS-2: Data, 1982 (Box 1 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 42)
  - STS-2: NOSL Critique, 1982 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 1)
  - STS-2: Preliminary Report, 1981 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 2)
  - STS-2: SCIENCE Magazine/NOSL Collaborative Issue, 1982 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 3)
  - STS-3: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 4)
  - STS-4, 1978 (Oversized 3, Folder 3)
  - STS-4, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 5)
  - STS-4: Crew Activity Plan Final PCN-1, 1982 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 6)
  - STS-4: Hasselblad Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 7)
  - STS-4: H.D. Voss, Lockheed, 1982; 1985 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 8)
  - STS-4: Log and Summary, 1982 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 9)
  - STS-5, 1982 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 10)
  - STS-5, 1982 (Oversized 3, Folder 4)
  - STS-6, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 11)
  - STS-6, 1982-1983 (Oversized 3, Folder 5)
  - STS-6: Crew Activity Plan, Revision A, 1983 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 12)
  - Technical Memorandum - Lightning Observations, 1980; 1984 (Box 2 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 13)
  - Technical Memorandum - Thunderstorm Observations, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 1)
  - Technical Memorandum - Luminous Electrical Phenomena, 1976 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 2)
  - U-2 Flight Proposals, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 3)
  - U-2 Flights, 1981 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 4)
  - U-2 Flights, 1983 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 5)
  - Venus Atmospheric Probe, 1979-1987 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 6)
  - Waldteufel, P., Soyouz Mission Flight, 1980 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 7)
  - Y Lightning, 1983 (Box 3 (2-NASA Experiments), Folder 8)
- Arthur D. Little, 1931-1971; Undated; 3; 5.8 cubic ft.
  While employed at Arthur D. Little, Dr. Vonnegut built upon his research in atmospheric science. The majority of his work focused on electrification of clouds, thunderstorms, and the behavior of lightning, he also looked at behaviors of gases but on a much smaller scale. Besides pursuing his own research, Dr. Vonnegut worked on a number of advisory projects for the United States government. These projects focused on the relationship between aircrafts and lightning. The main focus was on how aircrafts detect and avoid lightning when flying in a storm.
  The series contains data, reports, correspondence, press releases, photographs, newspaper clippings, drawings, figures, and handwritten notes. The arrangement reflects Dr. Vonnegut's original filing system. Materials are first filed by item type and then by subject. In cases where different types of materials were filed together, Dr. Vonnegut's arrangement was maintained to reflect how he used and viewed the materials. This is most prevalent in correspondence files. Correspondence is sometimes paired with clippings or reports. If the correspondence was separated from the items it was originally paired with, the archivist maintained this arrangement.
  - Advisory Panel for Weather Modification - NSF, 1953-1964 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 1)
  - Advisory Panel for Weather Modification - NSF, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 2)
  - Advisory Panel for Weather Modification - NSF, 1968; Undated (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 3)
  - Advisory Panel for Weather Modification - NSF, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Committee on Weather Control, 1954-1958 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 4-6)
  - American Geophysical Union Conference, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 7)
  - American Meteorological Society, 1958 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 8)
  - Analysis of Arthur D. Little by Electronatom Corp., 1955 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 9)
  - Atmospheric Electricity Studies, 1955-1958 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 10-11)
  - Atmospheric Physics Group Resume, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 12)
  - Blue Hill Meteorological Observatory, 1949; 1953-1955 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 13)
  - Brown, Dr. Ethan Allen, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 14)
  - Chemical Corps - Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 15)
  - Chemical Corps - Ozalids Case 63068, 1960-1963 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 16)
  - Cloud Chart, Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 6)
  - Comments on Thunderstorm Project, 1954 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 17)
  - Committee on Severe Storms, 1958-1960 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1949; 1952-1954 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 22-23)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, 1963; 1965-1966; 1968; Undated (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Chemical Corps, 1953; 1955-1956; Undated (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - "Electrical Behavior of an Airplane in a Thunderstorm, 1964-1965; 1971; Undated (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - General Electric Co., 1953 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - National Science Foundation Advisory Panel, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - National Science Foundation Advisory Panel, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - "ONR C-59667", 1956 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1953-1955 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1956 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1957 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1960 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1961 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Prospects and Proposals, 1962; Undated (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Research Discussions, 1957-1960 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Technical Papers, 1954-1956 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Technical Papers, 1957-1958 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Technical Papers, 1959-1960 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Technical Papers, 1961 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Technical Papers, 1961 (Oversized 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Technical Papers, 1962; 1966; Undated (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - Tornado Photography Contest, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - Tornado and Thunderstorm Theories, 1953-1962 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 1-3)
  - Correspondence - Tornado and Thunderstorm Theories, 1953-1962; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 7)
  - Data - "Indications Suggesting electrical Nature of Tornadoes", 1955 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 4)
  - Data - Jacksboro, Texas ONR-59667, 1951-1958; Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 5)
  - Data, Multiple Projects, 1948; 1962; 1964 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 6)
  - Data, Multiple Projects, 1948; 1962; 1968 (Oversized 3, Folder 7)
  - Dublin Symposium, 1954-1955 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 7)
  - Electrets Literature References, 1954 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 8)
  - Electrification - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955; 1961; 1963 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 9)
  - Electrification - Papers, 1953-1964 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 10)
  - Electrification Indicator (Poor Boy's Radar), 1955-1961 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 11)
  - Electrification Indicator (Poor Boy's Radar), Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 12)
  - Farewell Party Invites - Arthur D. Little, Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 13)
  - Federal Products Corp. Miniature Instrument, 1955 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 14)
  - "Final Report - The Detector of Atmospheric Electric Disturbances", 1964 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 15)
  - "Final Report - The Detector of Atmospheric Electric Disturbances," Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 16)
  - Final Report - Research on Electrical Phenomena Associated with Aerosols, 1962 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 17)
  - First Adirondack Conference on Atmospheric Nuclei, October 1957, 1954-1957 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 18)
  - "General Research Data" Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 19)
  - Handwritten Research Notes, Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 20)
  - Hastings-Raydist Incorporated, 1961-1965 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 21)
  - Inquiry Questions Related to Thunderstorm Electricity and Tornadoes, 1955 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 22)
  - International Conference on Cloud Physics, Sydney, Australia, 1961 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 23)
  - Kerivan, Leo, 1962 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 24)
  - Mt. Withington Study, 1957-1958; 1961-1962; Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 25)
  - Mueller, Eugene, 1964-1965 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 26)
  - New England School Science Advisory Council, 1960 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 27)
  - New England School Science Advisory Council, 1960 (Oversized 4, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper and Journal Clippings, 1967; Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Formation of Aerosols, 1966 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings -Thunderstorms, 1957; 1959; 1964-1966 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Weather Control, 1960; 1962; 1966; Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 32)
  - NSF Observatory, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 33)
  - Office of Naval Research - Case 68308, 1964-1966 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 34)
  - Office of Naval Research, Miscellaneous, 1954-1962 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 35)
  - Office of Naval Research Proposals Submitted, 1963 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 36)
  - Original Figures and Photographs, 1936; 1953; 1955-1956; 1959-1960; 1962 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 37)
  - Original Figures and Photographs, 1954 (Flat-file 2)
  - Original Figures and Photographs, 1958 (Oversized 4, Folder 9)
  - Original Figures and Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 38)
  - Ozalids, 1950-1962 (Box 3 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 39)
  - Ozalids, 1950-1962 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 1)
  - Papers on Thunderstorm Electricity, 1953-1962 (Oversized 7)
  - Popular Science - Tornadoes: Giant Electric Machines, 1960 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 2)
  - Proposal - Study of Origin and Role of Electricity in Clouds, Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 3)
  - Radar, Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 4)
  - Reports, "Adaptation of Carbon-Film Electric Hygrometer Elements to Industrial Use", 1953 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 5)
  - Reports - "The American Gas Association Thermal Precipitator", 1958 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 6)
  - Reports - "Apparatum for Continuous Measurement of Electrical Potential of Ionosphere", 1958 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 7)
  - Reports - Atmospheric Electricity, 1962; 1964 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 8)
  - Reports - "The Challenges of Weather Control", 1957 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 9)
  - Reports - "Cloud-Seeding Experiments over Sun Moon Lake Area", 1956-1957 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 10)
  - Reports, "Composite Materials via the Fluid-Bed Technique", 1963 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 11)
  - Reports - "Composition of the Heating of Air by Lightning Discharge", Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 12)
  - Reports - "The Effect of Atmospheric Conductivity on Space Charge Concentration in the Lower Atmosphere", 1956; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 13)
  - Reports - "Electric Potential Gradient Measurement Near Icelandic Geyser and Steam Plume from Geothermal Well", 1964 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 14)
  - Reports - "Electrical Behavior of an Airplame in a Thunderstorm", 1965 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 15)
  - Reports - "Electrically Charged Dust in Rooms", Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 16)
  - Reports, "Final Report on Development and Manufacture of Electric Hygrometer Elements for Meteorological Use to Camp Evans Signal Laboratory, Belmar, New Jersey", 1952 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 17)
  - Reports, "Investigation of Sampling Procedure Requirement", 1956 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 18)
  - Reports, "Investigation of Silver Iodide Decay and Transport and Natural Nuclei", 1955 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 19)
  - Reports, "lightning Does Not Terminate in the Percipitation Below the Cloud", 1931; 1948-1951; 1953-1955; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 20)
  - Reports - "Method and Apparatus for Measuring Electorstatic Fields in the Upper Atmosphere", 1959 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 21)
  - Reports - Misc. Reprint Information, 1947; 1955; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 22)
  - Reports - "Navigational Aid for Aircraft (P.M. Radar)", Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 23)
  - Reports - "Need for Physical Research in Meteorology", 1956 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 24)
  - Reports - "A New Electrostatic Precipitator", 1937 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 25)
  - Reports - "Observations of Thunderstorms in New Mexico", 1959 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 26)
  - Reports - "Ozalods for ONR C-59667", Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 27)
  - Reports, "Performance of Commercial Gas-Cleaning Equipment", 1958 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 28)
  - Reports, "The Possible significance of Atmospheric Space Charge in Cloud Electrification and Precipitation", 1956-1957 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 29)
  - Reports, "Preliminary Results of an Experiment to Determine Initial Precedence of Organized Electrification and Precipitation in Thunderstorms", Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 30)
  - Reports, "Prerequisites for Weather Control", 1957; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 31)
  - Reports, "Progress Report No. 48 on Improvement of Electrical Hygrometer Elements for Meteorological Use", 1950 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 32)
  - Reports, "Reaction of Sulfur in stack Plumes", 1966 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 33)
  - Reports, "Relationship Between Thunderstorm Electricity and Fair Weather Electricity" - R. Reviews, 1958; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 34)
  - Reports, "Research Projects to Imporve our Knowledge of Severe Storms", 1959; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 35)
  - Reports - "The Result of DvAer Support of the Atmospheric Electricity Study by Bernard Vonnegut - 1955 to 1958" (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 36)
  - Reports - Rough Drafts, 1955; Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 37)
  - Reports - "Sampling Procedure Requirements", 1957 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 38)
  - Reports - "Some Observations and Mechanisms of Charge Accumulation in Convective Clouds - Fitzgerald", Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 39)
  - Reports - "Space Charge in the Lower Atmosphere", 1956; 1958 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 40)
  - Reports - "Stabilization of a High Voltage Discharge by a Vortex", 1956 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 41)
  - Reports - "Study of Atmospheric Electrificattion and Proposal for an Extended Program" Office of Naval Research Geophysical Branch, 1955 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 42)
  - Reports - "Tornadoes at Blackwell, Oklahoma 5-25-55", 1956 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 43)
  - "Research in Electrical Phenomena Associated with Aerosols", 1960-1961 (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 44-45)
  - Rsearch in Electrical Phenomena Associated with Aerosols - Photographs and Diagrams, Undated (Box 4 (3-Arthur D. Little), Folder 46)